<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="category_info_anti_virus_1">Anti-virus products on Android don\'t provide the comprehensive protection that you\'re accustomed to from desktop operating systems such as \"Windows\".</string>
	<string name="category_info_anti_virus_2">Makers of anti-virus products may be overstating certain threats in order to profit financially.</string>
	<string name="category_info_anti_virus_3">On Android, every app runs in its own encapsulated container. This does not only mean that there are fewer possible attacks but also that even anti-virus products are running in such encapsulated containers and therefore don\'t have the power that they might suggest.</string>
	<string name="category_info_anti_virus_4">The biggest risk with mobile devices is that someone else gets access to your device. Therefore, anti-theft features may be the most important features in anti-virus packages.</string>
	<string name="category_info_firefox_1">You should prevent third parties such as advertising or analytics companies from tracking you on the web. To do so, press the menu button and choose \"Settings\". Then go to \"Privacy\" and set \"Cookies\" to \"Enabled, excluding 3rd party\".</string>
	<string name="category_info_firefox_2">To prevent third parties that try to track you on the web from knowing what sites you visit, you should disable this feature. To do so, enter \"about:config\" in the address bar and submit the input. On the following page, search for \"network.http.sendReferer\". Press the single search result and change the number from \"2\" to \"0\". Leave with the back button.</string>
	<string name="category_info_firefox_3">The app wants to send data to its servers over the internet so that it can improve its service. If you don\'t want this to happen, press the menu button and open \"Settings\". Then go to \"Mozilla\" and uncheck the four checkboxes \"Telemetry\", \"Crash Reporter\", \"Mozilla Location Service\" and \"Firefox Health Report\".</string>
	<string name="category_info_firefox_4">If you don\'t want to receive automatic recommendations for sites you may like based on your browsing habits, you should disable this feature. To do so, press the menu button and open \"Settings\". Then go to \"Customize\". Open \"Home\" and uncheck \"Show site suggestions\".</string>
	<string name="category_info_firefox_5">When searching, automatic suggestions during typing may be convenient. But if you want to disable this feature for privacy reasons, press the menu button and open \"Settings\". Then go to \"Customize\" and \"Search\". Uncheck \"Show search suggestions\".</string>
	<string name="category_info_keyboard_1">This keyboard has full internet access and can read every single letter that you type. It may, potentially, send usage data (or even full keyboard input) to servers over the internet.</string>
	<string name="category_info_launcher_1">\"Launcher\" apps are one of the most critical pieces of software on your device. In order to work properly, they need longs lists of permissions that may be abused, potentially. You should only install such apps from developers that you absolutely trust.</string>
	<string name="category_info_web_view_wrapper_1">This app is not really a full web browser but only wraps your device\'s default browser in a nicer packaging with a new interface.</string>
	<string name="category_info_web_view_wrapper_2">Consider using one of the state-of-the-art browsers that come with their own rendering technology. You may take a look at \"Firefox\", \"Opera\" and \"Google\".</string>
	<string name="category_info_web_view_wrapper_3">This browser\'s security and technology for website rendering depends on whether your device\'s default browser is up-to-date. Its updates don\'t enhance the technology for website rendering.</string>
	<string name="category_info_two_factor_auth">Remember that, whenever you switch to a new device or lose your current device, you need a backup for the logins that you protected with two-factor authentication.</string>
	<string name="category_info_insecure_clipboard">The system\'s clipboard, (where copied data is stored so that it can be pasted later, is insecure. This means that all apps can read it. You should definitely consider using settings that cause the clipboard to be automatically cleared after a short duration (e.g. 1 minute).</string>
</resources>
